{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Wèishéme",
      "answer": "为什么"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zuótiān",
      "answer": "昨天"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dōngxī",
      "answer": "东西"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wánr",
      "answer": "玩儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wǎnshàng",
      "answer": "晚上"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wǎn",
      "answer": "晚"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bàn",
      "answer": "半"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xiě",
      "answer": "写"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hànzì",
      "answer": "汉字"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shuìjiào",
      "answer": "睡觉"
    },
    {
      "question": "Qǐchuáng",
      "answer": "起床"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīnggāi",
      "answer": "应该"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wèntí",
      "answer": "问题"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kěyǐ",
      "answer": "可以"
    }
  ]
}
